Let it go. It's not a big deal.
그냥 좀 넘어가
별거 아니잖아
Not a big deal? It's amazing. You
reach in, there's one maneuver and bam!
별거 아냐?
대단한 기술이지
손만 넣어서 간단한 동작 끝에
브라를 소매에서 꺼내잖아
A bra. Right out the sleeve.
As far as I know, guys don't do
anything that comes close. Right?
내 상식으로는...
그 어떤 남자도 그런 건
흉내도 못해
내말 맞지?
남자들은 서서 소변보잖아
Come on! You guys can pee standing up.
그래?
나도 해봐야지
We can? Okay, I'm trying that.
내 생각을 말해볼까?
Know what blows my mind?
Women can see breasts
anytime they want.
여자들은 언제든지
가슴을 볼 수 있어
You look down,
and there they are.
그냥 내려다보면 있잖아
우리는 죽어도 못하는 걸
쉽게 하지
How you get any work done
is beyond me.
내가 못하는 걸 말해 줘?
I don't get how guys can do
so many mean things...
남자들은 못된 짓을 하고도
별 상관도 안 해
...and not even care.
-Multiple orgasms!
-There you go.
성적 만족은?
당연 여자 쪽이지
The One With the
East German Laundry Detergent
토요일 밤, 연인의 밤
토요일 밤!
Saturday night. The big night!
Date night!
Saturday night. Saturday night!
토요일 밤!
-No plans, huh?
-Not a one!
- 별 계획 없지?
- 절대 없지
Not even breaking up with Janice?
- 제니스 딱지 놓기도 못하고?
- 그래, 맞다
Right, right. Shut up.
닥쳐!
Chandler, nobody likes
breaking up with someone.
이별은 누구나 싫어해
그래도 해야지
Except for Kevin Millmore,
may he rot in hell.
-You just gotta do it.
-I know. But it's just so hard.
알아, 그래도 너무 힘들어
제니스는 상황 파악이
전혀 안 되는 여자야
You're sitting there with her.
She has no idea.
You finally get up
the courage to do it.
There's that awkward moment
when you've handed her the note.
마지막에 용기를 내서
말을 하려고 하면...
기이한 일이 벌어져
쪽지를 전하는 순간...
You try to run out of the restaurant
before she's finished the note.
Why do you have to break up with her?
Be a man. Just stop calling.
말로 해야할 이유가 있어?
사나이답게 해
전화를 하지마
너만 좋다면
나도 같이 할게
If you want, I'll do it with you.
She'd feel like
we're ganging up on her.
고맙지만 제니스는 패거리한테
당했단 기분이 들 거야
You dump Janice,
I'll dump T ony.
그게 아니라, 넌 제니스랑
난 토니랑 헤어지자구
- 토니?
- 헤어질 생각이야?
-You're breaking up with T ony?
-He's sweet, but it's not fun anymore.
착하긴 해도 재미가 없어
내 문제인지, 그 이 단식투쟁
때문인지 모르겠어
I don't know if it's me or
his hunger strike, I don't know.
Do you want anything else?
뭐 주문할 사람?
You had a nutty, chocolate-y,
kind of cake-y, pie thing that
지난주에 먹었던 거 좋더라
땅콩 초콜릿 케이크인지
파이인지 비스무리한 거...
Nothing. I' m fine.
아냐, 됐어
What's wrong? Why so scrunchie?
왜 그렇게 예민하니?
아빠 때문에!
My father wants to give me
a Mercedes convertible.
나한테 벤츠 오픈카를
사 주신대
That guy, he burns me up.
되게 화끈하시네!
Yeah, it's a Mercedes
if I move back home.
집으로 들어오면
사주신다는 거야
It was horrible!
He called me "young lady. "
너무 지겨워
나를 '어린 숙녀'라고 하셔
나도 우리 아버지가
그렇게 부르는 거 싫어
I hate when my father
calls me that.
Did he say
"You' re not up to this" again?
또 시작이시구나?
이런 건 생각도 못했지?
이번엔 디스코 버전으로
노래를 부르셔
I got the extended version
with choruses of...
... "You'll Never Make it on Your Own. "
"너 스스로는 절대
못 사는 차다"
Hi, Joey.
안녕, 조이
Oh, my God! Angela!
맙소사, 안젤라!
Wow! Being dumped
by you agrees with her.
너한테 차이고 나서
많이 달라졌네
- 저기로 가볼 거야?
- 아니
-Are you gonna go over there?
-No. Yeah. No.
응, 아니
Okay, but not yet.
I don't wanna seem too eager.
그래, 지금 말고
뜸을 들이다 가야돼
One Mississippi, two Mississippi...
1 미시시피, 2 미시시피
...three Mississippi.
That seems pretty cool.
3 미시시피...
이제 진정됐어
-Hey, Angela.
-Joey.
안녕, 안젤라
조이구나
You look good.
근사하다
That's because l' m wearing a dress
that accents my boobs.
가슴이 돋보이는 옷을
입어서 그래
You don't say.
동감이야
So, Rachel, what are you
doing tonight?
레이첼, 오늘밤에 뭐 할 거니?
신나게 보내야지
모니카랑 세탁소 갈 거야
Big glamour night.
Me and Monica at Launderama.
You wanna hear a freakish coincidence?
Guess who's doing laundry there too?
이렇게 기막힌 우연이 다 있냐?
누구도 거기 갈 거라는데...
-Who?
-Me!
- 누구?
- 나
Was that not clear?
기막힌 우연이지?
Why don't...?
너랑, 아니 너희들과
같이 가도 돼?
Why don't I just
join you both there?
Don't you have a laundry room
in your building?
아파트 건물 안에
세탁실 있잖아
Yes.
있지
I do have a laundry room
in my building.
거기에도 세탁실 있지
But there's a rat problem.
그런데 쥐가 들락거려
Apparently, they're attracted
to dryer sheets.
쥐들이 빨랫감에 맛을 들여서
빨래가 다 돼서 꺼내면 전부 다...
They're going in fine,
but they're coming out all fluffy.
털이 붙어있어
-Anyway, 7-ish?
-Sure.
- 7시 어때?
- 좋아
-Forget it. I' m with Bob now.
-Bob? Who the hell's Bob?
됐어, 조이
요즘 밥을 만나
밥?
대체 밥이 누구야?
Bob is great. He's smart,
sophisticated, and he has a real job.
좋은 남자야
똑똑하고 지적이고
진짜 직업도 있어
You go on three auditions a month
and you' re an actor. Bob
넌 오디션이나 보는 주제에
배우라고 하지?
- 하지만 밥은...
- 옛날을 생각해봐
Come on! We were great together.
And not just at the fun stuff,
but, like, talking too.
재미뿐 아니라
대화도 즐거웠지
Sorry, Joey. You said,
" Let's be friends. " So guess what?
미안해, 조이
그냥 친구로 지내자며?
그게 뭔지는 알지?
-What?
-We' re just friends.
뭔데?
- 그냥 친구로 지내는 거
- 알았어
Fine. Fine.
그럼 우리 넷이 함께
저녁 식사라도 하자
Why don't the four of us have
dinner tonight? As friends.
친구로서 말야
What "four of us"?
우리 넷?
너와 밥, 나와 내 여자친구...
You and Bob,
and me and my girlfriend...
... Monica.
모니카!
몇 번 말하냐?
이번엔 완벽한 남자야
I' m telling you,
this guy's perfect for you.
Forget it! Not after your cousin
who could belch the alphabet.
됐어!
트림이나 꺽꺽 해대는
사촌 소개한 게 언젠데?
Come on, this guy's great.
His name's Bob. He's Angela's...
이번에는 달라
밥이라는 친구는
안젤라의 오빠야
... brother. He's smart,
he's sophisticated...
똑똑하고, 지적이고...
진짜 직업도 있어
...and he has a real job.
I go on three auditions a month
and say l' m an actor, but he's
난 오디션만 보러 다니면서
배우라고 하지만, 밥은...
-God help us.
-What?
하느님!
왜?
Ugly Naked Guy
is laying kitchen tile.
벌거숭이 이웃남자가
부엌에 타일을 깔아
정말 부탁이야
Look, l' m asking a favor here.
If I do this for her brother,
maybe Angela will come back to me.
이번 일만 잘되면
안젤라가 맘을 돌릴 거야
What's going on?
You go out with tons of girls.
웬일이야?
여자라면 트럭으로 있잖아!
I know, but Angela's different.
그래...
하지만 안젤라는 달라
아주 다정한 여자야...
She's like one of a kind,
like a snowflake or....
-Something else like a snowflake?
-Yeah, yeah.
- 다정함이 전부인 여자?
- 그래, 맞아
Look, I made a huge mistake.
I never should've broke up with her.
내가 큰 실수를 했어
이별 선언을 괜히 했어
Will you help me? Please?
나 도와줄 거지?
제발...
Hold on a sec.
You need to not touch any of those.
잠깐, 제발 내버려둘래?
Okay, bye.
알았어, 끊자
Monica's not coming.
It's just gonna be me and Rachel.
모니카는 안 간대
레이첼과 단 둘이다
Hold on, camper.
You've thought this through?
잠깐, 정말 잘 할 수 있어?
It's laundry.
The thinking-through is minimal.
세탁소야
세탁만 잘 하면 되지
Just you and Rachel?
Just you two?
- 너와 레이첼, 단 둘이라며?
- 응
This is a date.
You're going on a date.
이건 데이트야
데이트라구!
-Uh-uh.
-Uh-huh.
아닐걸?
맞을걸?
-I haven't done that in a while.
-ls it a date if she doesn't know?
연애 감정을 다 잊었군
본인들도 모르는 데이트도 있냐?
Yes, absolutely.
Saturday night, all rules apply.
당연하지
어쨌든 토요일은 특별한 거야
그럼 어쩌란 거야?
What are you saying? I should
shave again? Pick up some wine?
면도를 또 해?
포도주라도 사?
- 더러운 속옷이나 치워
- 뭐?
Well, you may wanna rethink
the dirty underwear.
It's the first time she'll see
your underwear. You want it dirty?
그 더러운 속옷을 보이고 싶어?
지저분해 보일래?
No.
아니
And the fabric softener?
- 섬유 유연제도 치우고...
- 알았어
Okay, now what is wrong
with my Snuggles?
이 스너글이 어째서?
이건 말야, 섬세한 남자가
쓰는 세제로서...
What? It says I'm a sensitive,
warm kind of guy.
You know, like a little fuzzy bear.
곰 인형처럼 보송보송해져
- 가다가 딴 거 살게
- 당연하지
-I'll pick something else up.
-There you go.
오렐로스 피오렐로스 카페
Thank you.
고마워요
What does Bob look like?
Is he tall, short?
밥의 외모는 어떻대?
키 커? 작아?
Yep.
응
-Which?
-Which what?
- 어느 쪽이야?
- 뭐가?
-You've never met Bob, have you?
-No, but
그 남자 본 적도 없지?
그렇지만...
세상에, 만일 그 남자가
끔찍하게...
-For all we know, he's horribly
-Hey, Joey!
안녕, 조이!
끔찍하게 잘생겼네
입 다물게
Horribly attractive.
I'll be shutting up now.
Where are they? Where are they?
왜들 안 오지?
왜 안 오냐구?
난 좋아, 우리 둘이
뭐 하는 건 처음이지?
This is nice. We never
do anything, just the two of us.
Great. Maybe tomorrow we can rent
a car, run over some puppies.
그래, 우리 내일 차 타고
강아지라도 치고 다니자
그런 건 하기 싫어
I don't wanna do that.
- 시작이다!
- 그래, 이별 잘해
-Here we go.
-Have a good breakup.
-Hey, Janice.
-My God, I am so glad you called me.
안녕, 제니스
미쳐! 전화 줘서 고마워
오늘 정말 최고로
힘든 날이었거든
I had the most supremely awful day.
That's not good.
안 됐다
Can I get an espresso
and a latte over here?
여기, 에스프레소하고
라테 커피 주세요
We got the proofs from the shoot
with the vegetables. They sucked.
사진 다시 인화하라고 갖다 줬어
야채 들고 찍은 거 알지?
너무 흐리게 나왔어
그러느라 오후를 망쳤어
I blew off the afternoon.
I went shopping.
쇼핑을 갔는데, 자기 생각에...
이것저것 살펴보고, 또 보고...
And I got you....
I'm looking. I'm looking.
I' m looking.
-I got you
-What?
- 뭐야?
- 뭐?
-What?
-What did you get me there?
뭘 샀냐구?
바로...
I got you...
...these.
이거야!
Bullwinkle socks.
황소 양말
너무 귀엽다!
-That's sweet.
-I knew you had Rockys.
자기가 록키 양말 신는 거
알지만, 황소도 좋아
You can wear Bullwinkle and Bullwinkle
or Rocky and Rocky, or you can mix.
황소도 신고, 록키도 신고
한 짝 씩 신어도 좋지
Moose and squirrel.
Whatever you want.
사슴과 다람쥐도 어울릴 거야
I'm gonna get another espresso.
More latte?
난 한 잔 더 시킬래
라테 더 줄까?
아니
No, l' m still working on mine.
난 아직 시작도 안 했어
-That's it?
-Yeah, it was really hard.
벌써야?
너무 힘들었어
-Yeah, the hug looked pretty brutal.
-You weren't there.
포옹하는 꼴이 잔인하더라
그래, 넌 몰라
-Sorry.
-How are things going?
미안하다
제니스는 어때?
보면 몰라?
양말을 사왔잖아
Going? Things are not going.
She got me socks.
These go with your Rockys. She really
cares about you l' m sorry.
록키 양말이네
너를 많이 챙기는구나
안됐다
런더라마 셀프 빨래방
Coming through. Move. Move!
갑시다, 비켜요!
저기요, 잠깐만요
이 세탁기 제가 쓸 건데요
Excuse me! I was kind of
using that machine.
그래요? 이젠 아니네요
Yeah, well, now you' re kind of not.
But I saved it.
I put my basket on top.
제가 먼저예요
바구니를 올려놨잖아요
I'm sorry.
Is that your basket?
- 미안해요, 아가씨 바구니요?
- 그래요
It's pretty.
Unfortunately, I don't see suds!
아주 예쁘네
하지만 비누 거품은 없군!
What?
네?
No suds, no save, okay?
거품 없으면
시작 안 한 거 알죠?
What's going on?
- 무슨 일이야?
- 왔어? 아냐
Nothing. This horrible woman
just took my machine.
이 아줌마가 먼저 하겠대서
Was your basket on top?
네가 먼저 올려놨지?
- 응, 근데 비누거품이 없대
- 그래서?
-Yeah, but there were no suds.
-So?
-You know, no suds, no save.
-No suds, no Excuse me.
- 거품 없으면, 시작 안 한 거래
- 비누거품?
실례합니다
잠깐만요!
Hold on a second!
This is my friend's machine.
제 친구가 먼저잖아요!
Hey, hey, hey!
Her stuff wasn't in it!
이봐, 이봐
세탁기에 넣지 않았어!
이봐요, 아줌마!
여기 그런 규칙이 있나요?
Hey, hey, hey! That's not
the rule, and you know it!
All right. Show's over.
여러분, 빨래나 합시다
구경거리 아니요
Nothing to see here.
Okay. Let's do laundry.
어서 빨래나 하자
That was amazing!
I can't even send back soup.
- 대단하다!
- 그래...
난 그런 거에 안 익숙해
그거야 네가 너무 착하고...
Well, that's because you' re
such a sweet, gentle....
너 말이야...
Do you? Do you?
Oh, hey. You must need detergent.
세제도 넣어야지
-What's that?
-Uberweiss.
- 그게 뭐야?
- 우베르바이스!
It's new. It's German.
It's extra tough!
신제품, 독일제
엄청 세대!
Rach, are you gonna separate those?
그런 식으로 분류하니?
Oh, God.
Am I being a total laundry spaz?
아니, 너무 정신이 없어서
Am I supposed to use one machine
for shirts and another for pants?
셔츠와 속옷 종류를
따로 하는 거지?
Have you never done this before?
빨래 해본 적 없지?
혼자는 처음이야
여럿이는 해봤어
Well, not myself.
But I know other people that have.
Okay. You caught me.
I'm a laundry virgin.
그래, 걸렸다
나, 빨래계의 숫처녀야
Don't worry.
I'll use the gentle cycle.
걱정 마, 쉽게 알려줄게
좋아!
Basically, you wanna use
one machine for all your whites.
기본적으로 흰색을 따로 하고
- 흰색
- 그래
A whole other machine
for your colors.
- 색깔 옷은 다른 데 하지
- 색깔 옷
And a third for your...
세 번째로는 너의...
...delicates.
That would be your bras...
세심한 손길이 필요한
브라, 속옷... 팬티 같은 거
...and your underpanty things.
These are white cotton panties.
하얀 팬티는 어떡해?
흰색 쪽? 세심한 쪽?
Would they go with whites
or with delicates?
일단 생각 좀 해보자
That would be a judgment call.
He's so cute!
볼수록 멋있어!
Where did you grow up?
두 분 고향은 어디죠?
-Brooklyn Heights.
-Cleveland.
- 브룩클린요
- 클리브랜드
-How'd that happen?
-My God!
어떻게 그럴 수 있죠?
세상에나!
What?
- 왜?
- 왜 그래?
갑자기 기분이...
I suddenly had the feeling
I was falling.
가라앉아
But I'm not.
실은 아니야
안젤라와 댁과...?
So, you and Angela, huh?
네, 가깝죠
-Yep. Pretty much.
-You' re a lucky man.
- 운이 좋군요
- 네
Know what I miss most about her?
가장 그리웠던 게
뭔지 알아요?
쩝쩝대는 소리요
밥 먹을 때
That cute nibbly noise
she makes when she eats.
다람쥐가 뭘 갉아먹듯...
아님 족제비처럼
Like a happy little squirrel...
...or a weasel.
저는... 몰랐는데요
-I never really noticed.
-Oh, yeah, yeah. Listen for it.
잘 들어보세요
Monica. Monica is great.
모니카도 좋더군요
Yeah, she is.
네, 좋죠
But it's not gonna last.
오래 만날 순 없어요
She's too much for me in bed.
침대에서 너무 하거든요
Sexually.
성적으로 좀...
I've gotta tell you, Bob is terrific.
밥은 참 멋있어요
Yeah, isn't he?
네, 그렇죠?
It's great to meet a smart, funny guy
who's emotionally older than 8.
지적이고 재미있는 데다
성숙한 감성을 지녔어요
You know what else?
He's unbelievable in bed!
다른 장점도 있죠
침대에서 너무 좋아요
My brother never even told me
when he lost his virginity.
우리 오빠는 첫 경험도
얘기 안 해요
네...
That's nice.
좋군요
You can. It's like
pulling off a Band-Aid.
이렇게 해
반창고를 뗄 때와 똑같아
빨리 떼어내야
상처가 드러나지
Just do it really fast,
and then the wound is exposed.
Go! Go!
어서 해봐!
제니스?
Hi, Janice.
안녕, 제니스
Here we go. I don't think
we should go out anymore.
그래, 하자
우리 이제 그만 만나
제니스...
All right.
좋아
아주...
Well, there you go.
잘됐어
Stop it, stop it, stop it.
참아, 참아, 참아...
This isn't about you.
너 때문이 아냐
당연히 아니지
사랑을 두려워하는 너 때문이야
I know! It's about
your fear of commitment.
사랑을 두려워해?
난 전혀 두렵지 않아
I' m not afraid.
- 그럴걸?
- 아니야
-Please.
-I don't!
- 그렇다니까
- 아냐!
-I don't! I' m ready to commit anytime.
-Really?
- 난 언제든 준비가 돼있어
- 정말?
아주 멍청한 소리로
들리겠지만...
I know this is gonna sound stupid...
... but I feel that if I can do this...
할 수 있다는 자신감이 생겨
빨래도 할 수 있고...
...if I can actually do
my own laundry...
...there isn't anything I can't do.
이제 못할 게 없어
- 그건 멍청한 게 아냐
- 좋다
That does not sound stupid to me.
혼자... 저녁식사를 준비하는데
캐롤과 이혼한 뒤에...
The first time I had to cook
for myself after Carol left me
미안, 시간 됐네
2부에 계속!
I'm sorry, that's all the time
we have. Next on Ross....
-Uh-oh.
-What?
- 어오!
- 웬 '어오'야?
어오, 어오, 빨래가 끝났어
Uh-oh....
Uh-oh, the laundry's done.
It's a song.
노래야
빨래의 노래
The laundry song we sing.
Uh-oh! The laundry's done
"어오! 빨래가 끝났네
어오! 어오!"
-What's the matter?
-Nothing.
- 잘못 된 거야?
- 아냐
"몸을 숙여요
빨래가 끝났네"
The laundry's done
- 봐야겠어...
- 그래
Come on, show me.
흰 옷 속에
빨간 양말 하나가 있었어
It's just that you left a red sock
with your whites, and now...
그래서 모두...
...everything's kind of pink.
분홍색이 됐어
Everything's pink?
전부 다 분홍색?
응, 그래도 빨간 양말은
계속 빨개
Except for the red sock,
which is still red.
Don't be upset.
It can happen to anyone.
안 됐지만 화 낼 거 없어
누구나 겪는 일이야
But it happened to me.
지금은 내가 겪는 일이야
난 정말 구제불능인가 봐!
God, I'm gonna look like
a big Marshmallow Peep!
이게 무슨 짓이지?
아빠 말이 맞아
What am I doing?
My father's right!
I can't live on my own.
난 혼자 할 수 없어
빨래도 제대로 못 하잖아!
I can't even do laundry!
Something went wrong with Underdog
and they couldn't inflate his head.
개 모양 풍선이 이상했어요
머리에 바람을 못 넣더라구요
So anyway...
어쨌든...
그 머리가 곧장
브로드웨이로 날아갔죠
...his head is flopping
down Broadway, right?
And I'm thinking
how inappropriate this is.
그리고는 생각했죠...
부적절한 일이라구요
Something's in my eye. Could we
check it in the light, please?
눈에 뭐가 들어갔어요
밝은 데서 봐줄래?
-Oh, my God!
-What?
- 세상에
- 왜?
Were we at the same table?
It's like...
방금 전에 못 봤어?
원숭이 남매끼리
이 잡아 주는 거야?
...cocktails in Appalachia.
-They' re close.
-Close? Her tongue's in his ear.
- 친해서 그래
- 친해?
귀에 키스도 하는데!
Like you've never got
a little rambunctious with Ross.
너도 로스를 괴롭힐 때
있잖아
이건 아니지, 역겨워...
Joey, this is sick.
It's disgusting. It's...
전부 다 거짓이지?
... not really true' is it?
- 거짓이거나, 참이거나...
- 이게 무슨 짓이야?
Who's to say what's true?
-What were you thinking?
-l' m not proud of this, okay?
나 자신도 창피해
Well, maybe I am a little.
내가 좀팽이라 그래
-l' m out of here!
-Wait!
- 집에 갈래
- 잠깐, 기다려
You like him. I want her.
He likes you.
넌 저 남자 좋고, 난 저 여자 좋아
저 남잔 네가 좋고
-Really?
-Yeah.
- 정말?
- 그래
우리가 합심해서
저 둘을 갈라놓을 수 있어
If we put our heads together,
between the two of us...
...we can break them up.
I' m sorry.
I can't believe I did this.
미안해서 어쩌나
이럴 수가...
얘기가 너무 재밌어서
정신이 나갔나봐요
I couldn't stop laughing
at your Norman Mailer story.
Waiter? One more plate of
chicken wings over here.
웨이터! 닭 날개
한 접시 더 주세요
잘 들어, 제니스
우린 너무 달라
Here's the thing.
We're different.
난 이름대로 '빙빙' 대고
넌 성질대로 '붕붕' 대
I'm bing, bing, bing.
You' re boom, boom, boom.
맙소사!
정말 미안해!
Oh, my God! I' m so sorry!
Are you okay?
괜찮아?
It's just my lens. It's my lens.
렌즈 때문에 그래
괜찮을 거야
금방 올게
I'll be right back.
I hit her in the eye!
In the eye!
내가 눈을 쳤어!
눈을 쳤다구!
This is the worst breakup
in the history of the world!
이건 세상에서 가장
못 되 먹은 이별일 거다!
이런!
Oh, my God!
그 커피 몇 잔 째니?
-How many have you had?
-I don't know. A million!
몰라, 백만 잔?
Chandler, easy, easy.
Go to your happy place.
챈들러, 진정해
행복한 곳으로 갑시다
-l' m fine, l' m fine.
-All right.
- 난 괜찮아, 괜찮아
- 알았어
-l' m not fine. Here she is.
-Wait here, okay? Breathe.
나 안 괜찮아
온다... 이제...
쉬! 여기서 기다려
숨 쉬어
-How do you do that?
-It's like a gift.
비결이 뭐니?
천부적 재능이야
We should always break up together.
우리 항상 같은 날 이별하자
- 그거 좋지
- 좋아
I'd like that!
The clothes are clean.
That's the important part.
어쨌든 빨래를 했어
그게 중요한 거야
그런데 왜 죄다 끈적거려?
I guess. Except everything
looks like jammies now.
미안해요
실례지만, 이건 제 카트예요
I'm sorry.
Excuse me. We had this cart.
I had a 24-inch waist.
You lose things.
나도 허리 24인치였어
지금은 훨씬 굵지
자, 이제 비키시지
Now, come on.
Get out of my way.
죄송하지만 분명히 합시다
이건 제 카트예요
I' m sorry. Maybe I wasn't
being clear. This was our cart.
There weren't clothes in it!
이봐, 이봐!
여기 옷이 없잖아!
이봐요, 아줌마!
또 이상한 규칙이군요
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Quit making up rules!
비켜, 이건 내 거야
내가 먼저 봤다구!
Let go! Come on, it's my cart.
Listen, Mitzi, if you want it...
좋아요, 이걸 쓰고 싶으면
나를 함께 데려가시죠!
...you' re gonna have
to take me with it!
-Yes! Did you see that?
-You were incredible.
봤어?
- 아주 잘했어
- 봤지?
A brand-new woman,
ladies and gentlemen.
여러분
강한 여성 탄생입니다
Thank you. I could not have
done this without you.
- 네가 없었으면 못했을 거야
- 안돼, 이건...
이제...
건조기에 빨래도 꺼내야지
More clothes in the dryer?
괜찮아, 괜찮아
-I'm fine. I'm fine.
-Are you sure?
- 정말?
- 아니
-Are you sure you' re okay?
-Yeah.
- 정말 괜찮은 거야?
- 응
-Does it still hurt?
-Yeah.
- 아직도 아프지?
- 응
What a neat idea! All your
clothes match. I' m gonna do this.
옷 색깔을 깔끔하게 맞췄네
나도 이렇게 해야지
안녕
-How'd it go?
-Excellent!
- 오늘 어땠어?
- 아주 좋았어
We ripped that couple apart
and kept the pieces for ourselves.
그 커플을 갈라놓고
각자 한 쪽씩 맡았어
What a beautiful story.
- 아름다운 밤이었구나
- 그럼
-I'm fine, by the way.
-I'm sorry.
- 이 오빠 안 아프다
- 아니 어찌...
챈들러는?
-Where's Chandler?
-He needed time to grieve.
많이 속상한 가봐
I' m free! I' m free!
난 자유다!
That ought to do it.
저렇게라도 해야지